mycapture.com 2016-08-22

# Privacy Policy | Second Street

Second Street Media is committed protecting your privacy. As a user of the Second StreetMedia web site (the “Site”), you acknowledge that we will collect certain information about you, and that you may provide information regarding your tastes and preferences. Collected information is used to process your orders and personalize your experience. Required information is protected by secure server software. By using the Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Second Street Media and our affiliates. Any changes to Second Street Media’s Privacy Policy will be posted on this page so you will always be aware of information collected, use, and disclosure circumstances. This statement sets forth our Privacy Policy and describes the practices Second Street Media follows with respect to information provided by visitors to this Site. Please be aware that this Site contains links to other sites that are covered by their own privacy policies. Second Street Media welcomes your input. Please e-mail: support@secondstreet.com with questions and comments.

* * *

### Required Information

To purchase items via our Site and/or to become client, you must provide some basic name,email and other contact information. We use this information for internal purposes, namely,processing your orders, notifying you of your order status, updating your account, and sending you notices of special offers and promotions, new services, and noteworthy news and events. We do not sell or rent information about our customers or email lists to third parties. However, we may share this information with our partners and affiliates to enable them to provide you with special benefits, offers, and promotions. Our partners and affiliates privacy policies and practices may be different from Second Street Media, and we encourage you to become familiar with them. Second Street Media assumes no responsibility for these policies.

You can choose to not receive e-mails or updates about special benefits, promotions, or offers from Second Street Media, its affiliates, or its partners. You will be given the opportunity to elect not to receive such emails during the registration process. If you no longer wish to receive updates, you may update or correct this information by logging on to “Your Account” and editing your personal information or emailingsupport@secondstreet.com. We will endeavor to comply with your request as quickly as possible. Please note that if you opt out of receiving promotional material from SecondStreet, you still may receive such material from our worldwide partners, affiliates and as explained above.

Any personal data (such as age and gender) you may provide is used to create personalized content, services, and advertising on our Site, as well as to better understand the preferences of our members and customers. We may also aggregate your Site activity so that Second Street and our affiliates may better understand the users that are visiting our Site. In all cases, this aggregated data is anonymous and does not contain any personal information that identifies a user.

Second Street complies with the U.S.-Swiss SafeHarbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland. 

Second Street also complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union to the United States. Second Street has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles. If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification, please visit <https://www.privacyshield.gov/>

As part of the Privacy Shield Framework, Second Street is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the Federal Trade Commision (FTC). Individuals may invoke binding arbitration if possible, and under certain conditions. Second Street assumes liability for cases of onward transfers of EU data to third parties. Last, Second Street is required by law to furnish personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements. 

Per Privacy Shield regulations, Second Street has registered with JAMS as an independent alternative dispute resolution (ADR) service for EU members. More information can be found at: <https://www.jamsadr.com/eu-us-privacy-shield>

* * *

### Send to a Friend Feature

myCapture offers a “Send to a Friend” feature where users to the site can email links to specific photos around the Internet. myCapture uses the email addresses supplied for this purpose – both the referral and return email address – only to complete this service a single time. These email addresses are not stored, shared, or otherwise used for any purpose.

* * *

### Links

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Second Street Media is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

* * *

### Legal Disclaimer

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site.

* * *

### Change of Address or Contact Information

If your e-mail address or contact information has changed or is incorrect, you may update or correct this information by logging on to “Your Account” and editing your personal information.

* * *

### Security

When placing orders or accessing your account information, we offer the use of a secure server. The secure server software (SSL) encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us. Furthermore, all of the customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access. If you are just browsing the Site, a cookie identifies only your browser. If you become a registered online customer of myCapture or Upickem (with a designated user ID and password), we use cookies so that we can provide customized information that we believe will be of value to you based on preferences indicated, other information we have about you as a myCapture or Upickem customer, as well as information available from external sources such as the census bureau. It is possible to set your browser to inform you when a cookie is being placed. This way, you have the opportunity to decide whether to accept the cookie. If you are just browsing our Site and are not a registered online customer, you do not have to accept a cookie and you may continue visiting the Site.

If you have questions about Second Street Media Privacy Policy, please send an email to [support@secondstreet.com](mailto:support@secondstreet.com).

© Second Street Media. All Rights Reserved. Users of this Site agree to be bound by the terms of the Second Street Media Terms of Use. View Terms of Use and trademarks andPrivacy Statement of Second Street Media.
